Up next, daring daylight robbery
at a municipal swimming pool.
This is it. Turn me up.
Earlier today, a foul-mouthed bandit
robbed the municipal pool
making off with the contents
of over three lockers.
More like three lockers and a sink.
Bender, did you have
something to do with this?
Of course not.
Holy spitz.
He's sporting skintight Speedos.
They don't leave much to the imagination.
Actually on a robot, they sorta do.
One puny human got a look at the robber.
Here we go. Here we go.
Describing him as
a short, nasty, muscular...
Yeah, make me famous, bighead.
...Caucasian human male.
What?
Hey! Now what am I supposed to watch
and drink all day?
This is an outrage.
What's the point of pulling
the biggest pool caper ever
if nobody knows you did it?
Well, there's the material rewards.
You mean this junk?
Whee!
All I ever wanted was for people
to remember my name.
It's Bender.
Oh, fuff!
Why bother remembering anything?
You're just going to forget it
five seconds later.
It's so unfair.
A debonair robot with
a zesty, in-your-face outlook
doomed to obscurity like the rest of you,
especially Leela.
If I died tomorrow,
no one would even notice.
Boy, I've never seen him so down,
or ever before.
How does a nobody like me get famous?
I know.
Hey, look. I'm stuck,
but I haven't given up hope.
Call a soft-news journalist.
You're not stuck.
Shut up.
Hey, everybody, do the "Bender."
This move's called the "Bender."
Yo, Hot Wheels, this circle's about
free expression not fascist moves.
A blank wall. Fame is mine.
There. Now no one will forget how I live
or my attitude regarding butt.
All right, ladies. Let's flush
these artists' lofts straights to hell.
No!
I'm the first one to work. A new low.
- Surprise!
- Happy funeral, Bender.
A surprise funeral, for me?
We just wanted to show you
that you really will be remembered.
Now, if the deceased will kindly
take his place of honor.
Ooh! Cushiony. And a minibar.
Dearly beloved, we are here today
to remember Bender,
taken from us in the prime of life
when he was crushed by a runaway semi
driven by the Incredible Hulk.
Aw! You knew my favorite cause of death.
Now let us each remember the best things
about Bender, in our own way.
Professor?
Your standard bending unit
is made of an iron-osmium alloy.
But Bender was different.
Bender had a .04 percent nickel impurity.
It's what made me me.
If you ever needed a small package
brought into the country
without a lot of X-raying and such,
Bender always had a free body cavity.
The professor's was better.
Bender, shush. You're supposed to be dead.
Say more about how great I am.
And where's the crying?
You people look like
you're waiting for the bus.
Oh, Danny boy, the pipes
The pipes are calling
Who-y boy?
From glen to glen, and down...
Danny boy?
You're at my funeral, singing about
some dead stiff named Danny boy?
You really are a massive bonehead.
I'm expressing my sorrow.
Get lost.
I'd say, "Don't quit your day job,"
but you're awful at that, too.
We're trying our best.
Your best is an idiot.
Let's pick it up, people.
So far, it's been crap after crap.
I croaked. Now, show me some love.
Bender was a truly special...
Louder and sadder.
Next.
- Dear Lord...
- Oh, next.
Oh, Danny boy...
Come on. Surely there must be someone here
who knows how great I was.
Yes, there is, Bender.
Bender was a lot of things
to a lot of people,
but looking back, the number one thing
I can say about him is this,
and simply this.
Bender was my friend.
What? That's it?
Who are you? You're nobody.
This is the worst funeral ever.
I hope you're all happy.
You've succeeded in convincing me
life is worth living
by showing how bad my funeral will suck.
I know whose funeral
we'll be attending next.
Oh, stop.
News, everyone.
Today you're going to O'Cyris IV
to deliver this enormous sandstone block.
I thought something
looked different in here.
Hi. We have a giant stone
to deliver. Sign here.
Ah! Very nice. Much like
the ten million identical stones
already used in the future tomb
of our great Pharaoh Hermenthotip.
Impressive. Who's building it?
- You.
- Say again?
You are now slaves of
the great Pharaoh Hermenthotip.
Guards.
Call it a hunch, but I've got
a bad feeling about this.
You know, the worst thing
about being a slave,
they make you work
but they don't pay you or let you go.
That's the only thing about being a slave.
Attention. You are now possessions
of the great Pharaoh Hermenthotip,
heir to the tenth dynasty,
bringer of the good aspects
of the annual floods.
Incredible. This place is just like
the ancient Egypt of my day.
That is no coincidence.
For our people visited your Egypt
thousands of years ago.
- One.
- A billion.
We learned many things
from the mighty Egyptians.
Such as pyramid building, space travel,
and how to prepare our dead
so as to scare Abbott and Costello.
Also Wolfman.
Look at these swanky tombs.
These people really know how to die.
Are you crazy?
They worked thousands of people to death
to make these stupid monuments.
Hey, you spend your whole life
building a guy's toe,
you're gonna remember him.
I think I'm gonna like it here.
Yeah, I noticed your sign
and I thought I'd come over...
What we do is make you starve to death.
One, two, three, pull.
Oh! Bloody chunder.
Pick it up, people.
We're enslaved here to do a job.
Master, do we have to
count to three every time?
Couldn't we count to one?
Or better yet, one-half?
Good idea, slave. One-half, pull.
One-half, pull.
Now we're slaving.
Come on, guys.
Pharaoh's counting on us.
Work faster. Like this.
You call that motivating me?
Don't just whip with your arms.
The power comes from your hips. Like this.
Bender, quit giving
the slave drivers pointers.
Yeah. Remember who your real friends are.
I'll tell you who I remember.
Enupsis. Pleotut. What's-his-name.
He was the greatest of all.
Pharaoh Hermenthotip approaches.
Hurry, hurry. Pharaoh's coming.
Get that nose in place. Come on.
Excellent work.
I'm very proud of all you slaves.
Whoo hoo! Viva Hermenthotip.
And now, I have a grand announcement.
In honor of your achievement,
you're all hereby...
No!
Tell the slaves they can all go...
Go faster? I told them,
but they're so damn lazy.
No. I mean, they're all free.
Freeloading off you? I agree.
No, I...
Pharaoh Hermenthotip is dead.
He's whipping angels now.
We commend the body
of the great Hermenthotip
to the abode of the damned.
The damned good-looking.
Pharaoh commanded me
to tell that joke at his funeral.
I'll always remember you, Hermenthotip.
To equip Pharaoh for his journey,
we bury him with his favorite possessions.
Such as his heart and liver.
And the many goods he left
in his royal garage.
Also this bag of cats
our culture considers holy.
Pharaoh, my god king,
You are cold and deceased
I used to have him sing
P-P-P-Pharaoh and his pets
But the years went by
And Pharaoh died
Susie will have joined him
In the afterlife
Hermenthotip is gone.
The time to designate a new Pharaoh
is at hand.
Wow.
At dawn tomorrow, the high priest
will consult the Wall of Prophecy
to determine Hermenthotip's successor.
Whoo!
That concludes the funeral.
You don't have to go home,
but you can't stay here.
Can you believe it? Pharaoh's dead.
Yes. Tonight we are slaves to no one.
Except the rhythm.
Yeah. Play those bongos.
I'm gonna spin till I fall down.
Whoo!
We interrupt this ancient prophecy
to bring you a late-breaking bulletin.
Great Wall of Prophecy.
Reveal to us
God's will that we may blindly obey.
Free us from thought and responsibility.
We shall read things off you.
Then do them.
Your words guide us.
We're dumb.
You know what else stinks
about being a slave? The hours.
The prophecy is strange
and crudely drawn at best.
It indicates that we are here...
...and our next Pharaoh
is over there, near some tents.
Those are waves, jackass.
It's supposed to be a river.
Hey, I think I know
who the next Pharaoh is.
Oh, Lord.
We hear your voice, great Pharaoh.
Reveal yourself to us.
Behold. I have emerged
from the place of spells and fairies.
It is he, just as
the Wall of Prophecy prophesied.
Long live Pharaoh Bender.
This society is a bunch of idiots.
People of O'Cyris IV.
Please welcome a man
who started as a slave,
but worked his way up
to lord of all creation.
Our new Pharaoh, Bender.
Citizens of me. The cruelty of
the old Pharaoh is a thing of the past.
Let a whole new wave of cruelty
wash over this lazy land.
- Huh?
- What? What did he say?
Hear the word of Pharaoh.
Build unto me a statue
of ridiculous proportion.
One billion cubits in height
that I might be remembered
for all eternity.
And be quick about it.
Lowly slave. Why are you not working?
I am.
I meant, "Yourself to death?"
Mighty Pharaoh, it hurts when I breathe.
Well, then, what do you think
you should stop doing?
Crawl, pigs.
Ow!
The Pharaoh has spoken.
Your task is nearly completed.
Don't let down Pharaoh now.
The great monument
is finished, oh, Pharaoh.
And now the unveiling.
Hmm.
Remember me.
Does it please you, my lord?
Mmm.
It's a good start.
Yeah, it's definitely big, all right.
I just wonder if it's too big, you know?
I mean, are people gonna be
remembering me or the statue?
But, sire, we made it
to your exact specifications.
Too exact, if you ask me.
Tear it down and try again.
But this time, don't embarrass yourselves.
Yeah. That's right.
What...
Ladies and gentlemen,
the Pharaoh suddenly died.
Yay!
Good riddance.
What about my servants?
- Yeah.
- Right.
Bender, I really hope that's you,
because if it isn't...
we're in trouble.
You jerk. Why'd you have to drag us along?
I wanted to watch you remember me.
Did you really think you'd need
all this junk in the afterlife?
Afterlife?
If I thought I had to go through
a whole another life,
I'd kill myself right now.
Well, rot in peace. Fry and I are leaving.
Sorry, but we're totally sealed in.
Nothing can get in or out
except millions of snakes.
Here, have a pomegranate schnapps
from my private distillery
and start sharing
fond memories of me, Bender.
What proof is this? Some huge number?
It's explosive.
Maybe we could escape
by setting fire to the distillery
and blowing this place to rubble.
Let's get a little kindling going.
No! You can't blow up my monument.
I won't be remembered.
Oh, right. How selfish of me.
We'll just stay here forever.
Hey, Fry, remember that robot, Bender?
Bend-er? Doesn't ring a bell.
Did you hear something, Leela?
No, but I bet it wasn't someone
who was good at stealing.
Stop it. Stop it. It's not right.
You've crossed a line!
Hey, Leela, you know who I remember?
Oh, please let it be me.
That guy who used to bend things,
you know?
- Me? Please?
- Hermes.
All right, all right.
If it means that much to you,
blow up my statue.
Oh, Bender.
When did you come in? Hold still.
Let's blow this tomb.
Pharaoh Bender.
He once more walks among the living.
How we doing?
Remember me.
I will. I will.
Please just leave me alone.
Bender, I understand your desire
to be remembered,
but you don't need a statue for that.
I don't?
No.
You have your legacy as a brutal,
tyrannical dictator,
and that will outlive any monument.
You really think they'll remember me?
Absolutely.
Well, in that case, one planet down.
Helmsmen, set course for Earth.
That's not Earth.
Oh.